So, as we've seen so far,
これまで見てきたように
all our algorithms are numerical.
すべてのアルゴリズムは数値的です
This means we need to input numbers,
つまり テストのスコアや
such as a score in a test or the grades,
成績などの数値を入力する必要がありますが
but the input data will not always look like numbers.
入力データは必ずしも数値のようには見えません
Sometimes it looks like this.
このように見えることがあります
Let's say the module receives as an input
モジュールが プレゼントを受け取った事実
the fact that you got a gift or didn't get a gift.
または受け取っていない事実を入力として受け取るとします
How do we turn that into numbers? Well, that's easy.
これをどのように数値に変えるのでしょうか?簡単です
If you've got a gift, we'll just say that the input variable is 1.
プレゼントを受け取った場合は入力変数を1とします
And, if you didn't get a gift,
プレゼントを受け取っていない場合は
we'll just say that the input variable is 0.
入力変数を0とします
But, what if we have more classes as before or,
しかし以前のようにもっと多くのクラスがある場合
let's say, our classes are Duck, Beaver and Walrus?
あるいはクラスがアヒル ビーバー セイウチだったとしたらどうでしょう?
What variable do we input in the algorithm?
アルゴリズムにどのような変数を入力しますか?
Maybe, we can input a 0 or 1 and a 2,
0または1と2を入力できますが
but that would not work because it would assume dependencies between
存在しえないクラス間の依存性を仮定するので
the classes that we can't have. So, this is what we do.
動作しませんこれが実行した内容です
What we do is, we come up with one variable for each of the classes.
つまり クラスごとに1つの変数を考えます
So, our table becomes like this.
そのため テーブルはこのようになります
That's one variable for Duck,
アヒルの変数が1つ ビーバーの変数が1つ
one for Beaver and one for Walrus.
セイウチの変数が1つです
And, each one has its corresponding column.
また 各クラスに対応する列があります
Now, if the input is a duck then the variable for duck is
入力がアヒルの場合 アヒルの変数は1
1 and the variables for beaver and walrus are 0.
ビーバーとセイウチの変数は0です
Similarly for the beaver and the walrus.
ビーバーとセイウチについても同様です
We may have more columns of data but at least there are no unnecessary dependencies.
もっと多くのデータ列がある可能性がありますが 少なくとも不要な依存関係はありません
This process is called The One-Hot Encoding
このプロセスはOne-Hotコード化と呼ばれ
and it will be used a lot for processing data.
データ処理によく使用されます